onlinehealthny.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

* * *

### **What information do we collect?**

* * *

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or email to anna@healthmaxny.com.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

* * *

### What do we use your information for?

* * *

 **Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:**

* * *

  * personalize your experience
  * improve our website
  * improve customer service
  * administer a contest
  * promote products
  * offer a survey

* * *

 **How do we protect your information?**

* * *

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

* * *

 **We offer the use of a secure server.**

* * *

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.  ** **

* * *

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

* * *

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

* * *

###  **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

* * *

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

* * *

###  **Online Privacy Policy Only**

* * *

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

* * *

###  **Your Consent**

* * *

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

* * *

###  **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

* * *

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will send an email notifying you of any changes.

Hits: 23
